Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP); Records apap304
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty Records
1937-2023
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap304
18.89 cubic ft.
36.0 GB
This collection contains materials used by Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP) in its efforts to end capital punishment in Virginia.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted with the exception of select items noted in Series 5.
Acquisition Information
Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty first donated its records to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives in 2008. Michael E. Stone, executive director of Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, donated additional paper and digital materials in 2024.
Biographical History
Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty was founded in 1991 under the name of Virginians for Alternatives to State Killing by a group of 13 concerned citizens. In 1994 the group adopted the name, Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP). The organization sought a moratorium on the death penalty in Virginia and continued to educate the public about inconsistencies in capital punishment for three decades.
The VADP rallied against the death penalty in a number of ways, including execution vigils, non-violent protests, and lobbying. The VADP held yearly conferences that individuals could attend. Membership in the VADP was open to anyone who wished to join and was not restricted to just Virginia citizens.
The VADP worked to educate the public and legislators about the ineffectiveness of the death penalty in Virginia and Virginia's 21 day rule, a policy which prohibited trial judges from reviewing newly discovered evidence if it was presented more than three weeks after a defendant's sentencing. On March 24, 2021, Virgina Governor Ralph Northam signed legislation abolishing the death penalty, making Virginia the 23rd state, and the first in South, to stop executions. Having built support among legislators to pass the bill, VADP achieved its 30-year objective of a moratorium on capital punishment in Virginia. Having reached this goal, knowing other allies would continue to safeguard the death penalty moratorium and waiting two years to ensure that the legislation was not quickly reinstated, the VADP board elected to close the organization in February 2024.
Scope and Contents
The Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP) Records cover the entirey of the history of the organization's efforts, and success, to end the death penalty in Virginia. Physical materials included in this collection document the VADP's day-to-day activities such as petitions seeking an end to capital punishment in Virginia, Virginia General Assembly legislation, case law and legal education materials, subject files, newspaper clippings, scholarly articles, VHS tapes, and banners. Digital materials, added in the 2024 accession, include images, activity and planning documents, web news articles, documents relating to regional meetings, lobbying documents, digital equivalents of administrative documents such as tax forms, materials related to board activities, fundraising documents such as grant applications, planning documents, annual reports, letters, emails, and newsletters to members and non-members, and research materials from partnership organizations.
Although the VADP was established in 1991, a number of materials dated prior to 1991 are included in the collection, acquired by the VADP for research purposes.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Administration, 1984-2023
Series 2 - Legal, 1984-2022
Series 3 - Publications, 1975-2008
Series 4 - Communication, 1981-2022
Series 5 - Activities, 1992-2021
Series 6 - Petitions, 1993-2019
Series 7 - Subject Files, 1937-2023
Series 1, 2, 3, 5, 6, and 7 are arranged alphabetically while Series 4 is arranged chronologically.
Separated Materials
The archivist transferred four monographs: A Courageous Fool: Marie Deans and Her Struggle Against the Death Penalty by Todd C. Peppers, Closing the Slaughterhouse: The Inside Story of Death Penalty Abolition in Virginia, Railroaded: The True Stories of the First 100 People Executed in Virginia's Electric Chair and Virginia State Penitentiary: A Notorious History all by Dale Brumfield to the book division of Special Collections. They will be catalogued and included in the University Library Catalog.
Death Penalty; Capital punishment--Virginia; Capital punishment--Moral and ethical aspects; Juvenile justice, Administration of--Virginia; Bills (legislative records); Files by subject; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Petitions; VHS; Digital Files; Abolition movement--United States; Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty
- Administration, 1984-2023; 1; 2.2 cubic ft.; 3.39 GB
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of administrative materials of Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty from the history of their various establishing documents, including their previous names such as Virginians Against State Killing (VASK), to records that reflect their organizational functions such as Board Meeting materials, tax documents, financial documents, annual reports, fundraising letters, strategy documents, and award luncheons. There are also materials surrounding partnerships with other related organizations such as 8th Amendment Project as well as multiple grant applications, awards, and communications from organizations such as the Death Penalty Mobilization Fund (DPMF), The Tides Foundation, Cathedral of Sacred Heart, Church of Epiphany, Daughters of Wisdom, The Advocacy Fund, Shepard's Grant, Sisters of Bon Secours, and St. Mary's Human Concerns Endowment. A majority of the documents surrounding the succesful abolition of the death penalty in Virginia can be found here.
  Please note that a majority of this series contains born-digital files.
  Content Warning
  This series may contain graphic and potentially traumatic descriptions of executions and their circumstances. The original descriptions may contain harmful language or fail to demonstrate sufficient empathy for the subjects they depict.
  - 8th Amendment Project Fall 2018 Request for Proposals, VADP Proposal Narrative, 2018 August 9
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal, 2020 August 10
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal, 2020 August 12
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal Final, 2020 August 14
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal Final, Revised, 2020 August 17
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal, Draft, 2020 August 11
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal, Draft, 2020 August 12
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal, Draft, 2020 August 13
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP 2021 Grant Proposal, Draft, 2020 August 14
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP Application, Narrative Draft, 2019 August 21; 2020 December 31-2021 January 1
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP Cover Letter, 2019 August 20
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP Cover Letter 2020, 2020 August 10
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP Fall 2018 Proposal Cover Sheet, 2018 August 8; 2018 July 26
  - 8th Amendment Project VADP Proposal Information, 2019 August 23; 2020
  - "The 16 counties with the most executions, not including Texas (major cities within county in parentheses)" Graphic, 1976-2013 January 1; 2018 November 6
  - 1000th Execution, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1993 Virginians Against State Killing Commonwealth of Virginia Articles of Incorporation, 1993 March 4; 2016 October 3
  - 1995 Commonwealth of Virginia State Coroporation Commission Amendments, 1995 December 5
  - 1995 VADP Amendments-Commonwealth of Virginia State Corporation Commission, 1995 December 5; 2016 October 3
  - 1997 Commonwealth of Virginia State Coroporation Commission Amendments, 1997 November 21
  - 1997 VADP Amendments-Commonwealth of Virginia State Corporation Commission, 1997 June 15; 1997 October 25
  - 2001 VADP Award Banquet, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2007 Articles of Amendment & Reinstatement by Jon Sheldon, 2007 November 1
  - 2009 VADP Short Form Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax, 2010 June 23
  - 2012 Annual Report for VADP from Commonwealth of Virginia State Commission, 2012 March 31
  - 2012 Tides Letter of Interest Draft, Suggested by MES, 2012 May 9
  - 2012 Tides Letter of Interest Narrative, Final, 2012 June 26
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 2013 July 15
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 2013 July 18
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 2013 July 30
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 2013 August 26
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 2013 September 20
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 2013 November 5
  - 2013 Budget Projections, 25 hours per week, 2013 February 12
  - 2013 Profit Loss Statement Balance Sheet, 2014 August 7
  - 2013 Tides Letter of Interest Draft 2, Suggested by MES, 2012 May 10; 2012
  - 2014 Annual Report, Commonwealth of Virginia State Corporation Commission, 2014 March 31
  - 2014 Budget Projections, Full-time, 2013 April 25
  - 2014 Grant Final Report, General Support, 2015 October 30; 2015 October
  - 2014 Grant Final Report, Legislative, 2015 October; 2015 October 30
  - 2014 Grant Interim Report, General Support, 2015 March 20; 2015 March 30
  - 2014 VADP Grants Committed Chart, 2012-2014
  - 2015 Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2015 Budget Draft, 2015 July 17
  - 2015 Budget Draft, 2015 July 22
  - 2015 Budget Draft Revision, 2015 September 22
  - 2015 Budget Projections, Part-time June 1, 2013 April 25
  - 2015 Capacity Building Grant Final Report, 2015 November 18; 2015 November
  - 2015 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Narrative Draft, 2015 July 13; 2015 July 27
  - 2015 End Year Fundraising Campaign, Results, 2016 January 7
  - 2015 Essential Guide for Email Marketing, 2015 October 20
  - 2015 Fundraising Letter, 2015 April 21; 2015 April 27; 2015 April
  - 2015 Fundraising Letter, 2015 April 30; 2015 April; 2015 May 1
  - 2015 Fundraising Letter, 2015 April 28; 2015 April; 2015 May 1
  - 2015 Grant Final Report, Severe Mental Illness Strategic Advocacy Draft, 2016 October 21
  - 2015 Grant Final Report, Severe Mental Illness Strategic Advocacy Draft, 2016 March 31
  - 2015 Grant Interim Report, Legislative, 2015 March 20; 2015 March 30
  - 2015 Legislative Victory Story "Huge Victory Over Secrecy in Executions", 2015 June 17
  - 2015 Letter to Blessed Sacrament Alexandria New Pastor, 2015 July 9
  - 2015 May Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations, 2015 May 30
  - 2015 May Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2015 June 11; 2015 June 12
  - 2015 May Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, Final, 2015 September 7
  - 2015 Meet Executive Director "Michael Stone" Story, 2015 June 19
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2015 October 27; 2015 November 24
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2016 April 25
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Draft, Dan Shaws Edits, 2015 October 27
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Draft, Dan Shaws Edits & MES Changes, 2015 October 27
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Draft, Dan Shaws Edits & MES Changes, Revised, 2015 November 4
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 January 26
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, Final, 2016 January 12; 2016 January 26
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Final
  - 2015 November Fundraising Letter Final Response Card, 2015 November 9
  - 2015 Tides Death Penalty Capacity Building Grant Request, 2015 May 22; 2015 May 27
  - 2015 Tides Death Penalty Capacity Building Grant Request, VADP Matching Grant, 2015 September 27; 2015 September 26
  - 2015 Tides Death Penalty Mobilization Fund & Themis Funding Allocations Process, 2015 June 2
  - 2015 Tides Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Spending Table, 2015 October 1-2016 September 30; 2016 October 18
  - 2015 Tides Foundation Cover Sheet, 2015 July 27
  - 2015 Tides Themis Fall RFP for VADP- Strategy Area 3 Mental Illness, 2015 June 23
  - 2015 VADP Finances, 2006; 2008; 2010-2016 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2016 Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2016 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Final Report, Draft, 2017 July 10
  - 2016 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Narrative Draft, 2015 July 15; 2015; 2015 July 27
  - 2016 Grant Final Report, Severe Mental Illness Strategic Advocacy, 2015; 2016 October 21
  - 2016 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990, 2017 January 3
  - 2016 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990, Final, 2017 January 3
  - 2016 May Fundraising Letter Recipients, 2016 May 5
  - 2016 Narrative Draft, 2016 July 26
  - 2016 Narrative Draft, 2016 July 26; 2016 July 27
  - 2016 Narrative Draft, 2016 July 28
  - 2016 Narrative Draft, 2016 August 4
  - 2016 National Abolition Conference in Utah- Roster, 2016 September 2
  - 2016 Themis & Death Penalty Mobilization Fund 2016 Allocation Process, 2016 July 7
  - 2016 Tides Death Penalty Capacity Building Grant Request, VADP Fundraising, 2017 February 10
  - 2016 Tides Death Penalty Capacity Building Grant Request, VADP Web Site, 2015; 2015 May 22
  - 2016 Tides Death Penalty Capacity Grant Program, Request for VADP Fundraising, 2017 February 10
  - 2016 Tides DPMF Grant Spending Table, 2017 July 10; 2016 November 1-2017 October 31
  - 2016 Tides Grant Cover Sheet, Draft, 2016 August 3
  - 2016 VADP Finances, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2017 Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2017 Annual Report, Finance Page, 2018 February 23
  - 2017 April Fundraising Letter Final, Response Card, 2017 April 7; 2017 April 17
  - 2017 Budget Template, 2017 August 1
  - 2017 Cover Sheet, 2017 August 1
  - 2017 Cover Sheet Draft, 2017 August 1
  - 2017 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Final Report, Revision, 2016; 2017 July
  - 2017 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Report, 2018 August 8
  - 2017 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Report, 2018 July 31
  - 2017 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Narrative Draft, 2015; 2015 July 20; 2015 July 27
  - 2017 Grant Final Report, Severe Mental Illness Strategic Advocacy Revised, 2015; 2016 March 31
  - 2017 IRS Form 1099-K from PayPal, 2018 February 9
  - 2017 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990 Executive Director, 2018 February 9
  - 2017 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990 Field Director, 2018 February 9
  - 2017 Monthly Financial Reports (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2017 Narrative Draft, 2017 July 28
  - 2017 Narrative Draft, 2017 July 31
  - 2017 Narrative Draft, 2017 August 2
  - 2017 Narrative Draft, 2017 August 3
  - 2017 Staff & Board Bios
  - 2017 Staff & Board Bios, Draft
  - 2017 Tides Capacity Building Grant Spending Table, 2017 December 1; 2017 April 1-2018 March 31
  - 2017 Tides Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Spending Table, 2017 December 1; 2017 November 1-2018 October 31
  - 2017 VADP Annual Report Cover Page, Final, 2018 February 19
  - 2017 VADP Statement of Financial Position Balance Sheet, 2017 December 31; 2018 January 8
  - 2018 Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2018 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Final Report, 2016; 2017 July
  - 2018 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Narrative Draft, No Revisions, 2015; 2015 July 13; 2015 July 27
  - 2018 Grant Final Report, Severe Mental Illness Strategic Advocacy, 2015; 2016 March 31
  - 2018 IRS Form 1099-K from Paya, 2019 February 15
  - 2018 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990- Field Director, 2019 February 4
  - 2018 Narrative Draft, 2018 July 26
  - 2018 Narrative Draft, 2018 August 1
  - 2018 Narrative Draft, 2018 August 1
  - 2018 Narrative Draft, 2018 August 7
  - 2018 Narrative Draft, 2018 August 7
  - 2018 Narrative Draft, 2018 August 9
  - 2018 Proposal Budget Template from 8th Amendment Project, 2018 July 31
  - 2018 Proposal Budget Template from 8th Amendment Project, 2018 July 31; 2019
  - 2018 Proposal Guidelines from 8th Amendment Project, 2018 July 26
  - 2018 Reception Catering Proposal- Lucia's Resturaunt, 2018 December 6
  - 2018 Staff & Board Bios, Draft
  - 2018 VADP Finances, 2018-2019 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2018-2019 Awards Luncheon (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2019 Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2019 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Final Report, Final, 2016; 2017 July 13
  - 2019 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990- Executive Director, 2020 February 19
  - 2019 VADP Awards Luncheon (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2019 VADP Finances, 2010-2020 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2020 VADP Finances, 2020-2021 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Budget Template from 8th Amendment Project, 2020 August 6
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy, Draft, 2020 July 2
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy, Draft, 2020 July 2
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy, Final, 2020 July 7
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy, Final Budget, 2020 July 7
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy, Final Revision, 2020 July 9
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal - Virginia Interfaith Center for Public Policy, MES Edits, 2020 July 6
  - 2020 Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Proposal Form from 8th Amendment Program, 2020 August 6
  - 2020 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990, 2021 January 20
  - 2020 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990- Dale Brumfield, 2021 January 27
  - 2020-2021 VADP Annual and Special Report (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2021 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990, 2022 February 7
  - 2021 VADP Finances, 2021-2022 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2022 Lobbying Hours for IRS Form 990, 2023 February 7
  - 2022 VADP Finances, 2022-2023 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 501(c)(3) Application, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 85 Recommendations, 2005; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ABA Report on Virginia's Death Penalty "Tinkers with the Machinery of Death", 2013 September
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 April 7
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 May 10
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 May 25
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 June 29
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 July 21
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 August 19
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 September 27
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, 2021 November 15
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, Final, 2021 October 29
  - Abolition Victory Event, Planning Team Agenda, Revised, 2021 August 19
  - Accountant Contact Information, 2011 June 6
  - ACLU Survey and Results, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Action Plans from 2011 VADP Board Retreat, 2011 June 2
  - Activity Updates, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Addresses Change, 2020 January 15; 2020 March 6
  - Advice - Notes from Panel Event "Saying the Number," Presented by the Moose Management Academy, 2016 June 30; 2016 July 5
  - Aimee Board Member Agreement with VADP, 2007 October 10
  - "Albert" Biography, Undated
  - Alcohol Policy at The Cultural Arts Center, 2021 June 30
  - All Church Donors, Past Two Years and Locations, 2009-2011; 2011 May 5
  - "All Hands on Board: The Board of Directors in an All-Volunteer Organization" by Jan Masaoka, 1999
  - "Allies" Language Document, 2008 August 7
  - All Donors Report, Past Two Years, 2009-2011; 2011 May 5
  - All Time Major Donors, 2011 May; 2016 February 16
  - Amazing Raise, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Amazing Raise Authorization to Publish Portrait Signed, 2015 August 14
  - Amazing Raise Donations, 2015 September 17
  - Amazing Raise Donations, Final, 2015 September 17
  - Amazing Raise Donations, Net Proceeds, 2015 September 17; 2015 December 29
  - Amnesty International Chapter Talk, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 2018; 2019 January 28
  - Annual Report, 2019; 2020 February 7
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, 2016 March 14; 2016 March 10
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Draft 1, 2019 February 18
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Draft 1, 2020 February 14; 2020 January 31
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Draft 1, 2021 March 22; 2021 April 19
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Draft 2, 2019 February 18
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Draft 2, 2020 February 14; 2020 February 3
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Draft 2, 2021 March 22; 2021 April 21
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Final, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Final, 2019 February 18
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Final, 2020 February 14; 2020 February 3
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Final, 2021 March 22; 2021 March 16
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Final, Merged, 2021 March 22; 2021 March 16
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Final, Merged, Revised, 2021 March 22; 2021 March 17
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Finals, Fields, 2021 March 22; 2021 March 16
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Funds Generated, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Merged, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Merged, 2018 February 28; 2018 February 15
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Merged, 2019 February 18
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Merged Fields, 2020 February 14; 2020 February 3
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Merged Final, 2020 February 14; 2020 February 3
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients, 2018 February 28; 2018 February 12
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients, 2018 February 28; 2018 February 13
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients $50-99, 2018 February 28; 2018 February 13
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients Final, 2018 February 28; 2018 February 13
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients Misprinted, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Recipients Revised, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Revised, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Revised, 2018 February 28; 2018 February 15
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Donors, Second Revision, 2017 February 28
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Labels, 2016 March 14; 2016 March 10
  - Annual Report Cover Letter to Major Merged, 2016 March 14; 2016 March 10
  - Annual Report Cover to Major Donors, Recipients, 2020 February; 2020 February 3
  - Annual Report Cover to Major Donors, Recipients, 2021 April; 2021 March 16
  - Annual Report Cover to Major Donors, Recipients, 2019 February; 2019 January 25
  - Annual Report Cover to Major Donors, Recipients Revised, 2019 February; 2019 February 8
  - Annual Report Cover to Major Donors, Recipients Revised, 2020 February; 2020 February 3
  - Annual Report Filing Confirmation, 2011 February 14
  - Annual Report For Commonwealth of Virginia, 2008; 2008 March 31
  - Annual Report Mailing to Major Donors, 2016 March; 2016 July 22
  - Annual Report Mailing to Major Donors, Funds Generated, 2018 February 28; 2018 April 16
  - Annual Report Mailing to Major Donors, Funds Generated, 2019 February 18
  - Annual Report Mailing to Major Donors, Funds Generated, 2021 March 23; 2021 May 5
  - Annual Report Mailing to Major Donors, Funds Generated, 2020 February 11; 2020 April 15